And yes, so as you see, this is the homepage that we got over here.
We can create with AI or edit with AI or design from scratch.
All of these options will be available to us.
And as you see, based on our purpose, we can choose.
So I can say images, icons, wallpapers, invitations, banners, posters, social posts.
I don't know, greeting cards, stickers, monograms, coloring book pages.
Those drawings that mostly kids use and color, and this is fun for them.
So these are what I'm talking about, coloring pages, right?
Or we can have avatars, collages, emojis, and cliparts.
And we also can edit, so we can edit images, remove backgrounds,
generative arrays, you know?
So when it comes to an image that you want to remove a certain object from it,
this will be useful.
We can upscale, we can frame images, and we also can design from scratch.
So what we also have categories over here, you know?
Productivity, social media, print, paper, and photo.
And we can create and, you know, start designing over here.
So let me come back to create with AI.
And let's say that I want to get started with creating an image, right?
So the easiest part.
So we also can come here and click on create with AI.
And all of them available options will be seen and visible over here as well.
So as you see, we can have graphics, avatars, backgrounds, cliparts, emojis, etc.
And we can have designs like banners, collages, coloring, pages, etc.